

FRONT-END DEVELOPER & DESIGNER

CONTACT ME

514 588 8189

cecile .1612@hotmail.com

in Cecile Bemboy

My website: https://...

SOFT & TECHNICAL SKILLS

- · Capacity to communicate and collaborate effectively with colleagues
- · Ablity to be open-minded to advice, constructive criticism and other ways of doing things
- · Committed to lifelong learning

Front-end	Back-end	Graphic Design
HTML	Node.js	Figma
CSS	Python	Photoshop
Bootstrap	No SQL Databases	InDesign
JavaScript		Illustrator
JQuery		
React.js		

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATION

2013 - 2016 **GRAPHIC DESIGN**

Dawson College

Graduated with Honors

2022 **UDEMY**

> Complete Web Development Bootcamp

LANGUAGE SKILLS

English & French (both fluent)

ABOUT ME

I'm a graphic designer by trade who's worked extensively on building technical skills with various front-end languages towards becoming a front-end developer. I've learnt important transferable skills from my past working experience that will benefit me in an entirely new and challenging industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

GROUP DYNAMITE - Ville-Saint-Laurent **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

July 2018 - May 2019

- Developed a wide variety of apparel designs (graphics) and prints (AOPs, YDS) that are aligned with the overall seasonal design direction and emerging trends.
- Managed deadlines in accordance with the corporate calendar.
- Created technical artwork packages for submission to factory.
- Creatively explored different apparel techniques, colors and materials.
- Maintained project libraries and reference materials.

L'IMAGE HOME PRODUCTS — Downtown Montreal **GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

June 2016 - June 2018

- Executed design concepts for packaging artworks while meeting and maintaining customer/company brand requirements and guidelines.
- Responsible for researching ideas/images, obtaining die lines, creating line arts and preparing files for submisssion to factory (preflight).
- Verified proper layout, text and color file and confirmed or disapproved approval of factory artwork proofs for new and existing items.
- Prepared Pre-production Sample and Golden Sample reports to send to factory.
- Worked with photographer; prepared item(s) and briefing for product shoot as required.
- Produced marketing materials such as advertisements, mockups, sales sheets and pointof-purchase displays.

SECOND CUP CAFÉ - Downtown Montreal **BARISTA**

December 2014 - 2022

Served european coffee, viennoiserie and merchandise to customers while ensuring all their needs are met by engaging with them to guarantee their visit is a pleasant one. High priority is maintaining cleanliness and presentation of the cafe.